1490305057557,-360,'{"status": "ABANDONED_BY_TIMEOUT", "start_timestamp": 1490304457406, "name": "Thought Shakeup", "trigger_type": "USER", "question_answers": [{"status": "ABANDONED_BY_TIMEOUT", "completion_time": 1490305057426, "start_time": 1490304495701, "questions": [{"question_text": "The unpleasant thoughts that cross our minds are often exaggerated or inaccurate.\n\nThe following exercise is designed to help you shakeup your thoughts. You can use it to evaluate your thoughts, examine how accurate they are, and replace them with more accurate thoughts.", "prompt_time": 1490304657074, "completion_time": 1490304505393, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 0}, {"question_text": "Think about an unpleasant thought you are currently having.\n\nPlease type that thought in the box below. You can still continue with the exercise even if you don''t type anything.", "prompt_time": 1490304685521, "completion_time": 1490304657066, "question_type": "edittext", "response": ["I''m already unhealthy, so smoking is not that big a deal in the big picture"], "question_id": 1}, {"question_text": "How true do you believe this thought is?", "prompt_time": 1490304690892, "completion_time": 1490304685506, "question_type": "seekbar", "response": ["76"], "question_id": 2}, {"question_text": "On the following screens there are some questions regarding your thought.\n\nThere are no correct or incorrect answers. Please select the response that seems most correct for you.", "prompt_time": 1490304713621, "completion_time": 1490304690865, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 3}, {"question_text": "My thought is based on a \"all-or-nothing\" or \"extreme\" view. For example, \"If I am not the absolute best, it means I''m worthless\".", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490304725730, "completion_time": 1490304713615, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Strongly Agree"], "question_id": 4}, {"question_text": "My thought is affected by my focus on the negative aspects of the situation rather than the whole picture.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490304743226, "completion_time": 1490304725715, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Agree"], "question_id": 5}, {"question_text": "My thought is affected by the idea that everything is related to me or caused by me. It doesn''t take into account external circumstances or other people''s responsibility.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490304768736, "completion_time": 1490304743200, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Neither agree or disagree"], "question_id": 6}, {"question_text": "My thought is affected by what I''ve decided others think about me, even if this is not what they really think.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490304779411, "completion_time": 1490304768729, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Strongly Agree"], "question_id": 7}, {"question_text": "My thought does not take into account my successes or good qualities.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490304801376, "completion_time": 1490304779397, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Agree"], "question_id": 8}, {"question_text": "My thought is influenced by the overly negative consequences I think certain events or conditions will have on my future.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490304974580, "completion_time": 1490304801353, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Neither agree or disagree"], "question_id": 9}, {"question_text": "In the box below, use the provided sentence starters to come up with reasons why your thought may be correct or incorrect.\n(please click \"done\" to continue)", "prompt_time": 1490304990662, "completion_time": 1490304974572, "question_type": "edittext_special", "response": ["weight, mental health, physical activity is low", "I don''t really take care of myself", "smoking is already causing a cough and making it harder to do simple things", "living paycheck to paycheck because of smoking cigarettes is ruining longterm goals"], "question_id": 10}, {"question_text": "Please take a moment to review your answers to the previous questions and reflect on how your thought might be phrased differently taking these answers into account.", "prompt_time": 1490304990617, "completion_time": 1490304990611, "question_type": "text_review", "response": null, "question_id": 11}, {"question_text": "Try rephrasing your thought in a way that reflects reality as accurately as possible. The new wording does not need to be more positive, just more realistic.", "prompt_time": 1490304990681, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "edittext", "response": ["q"], "question_id": 12}, {"question_text": "How correct is your new thought\n(Touch and drag)", "prompt_time": 1490304990703, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "seekbar", "response": ["50"], "question_id": 13}, {"question_text": "Read your original thought again. How correct do you think it is?\n(Touch and drag)", "prompt_time": -1, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "seekbar", "response": null, "question_id": 14}, {"question_text": "Our negative thoughts often make things seem worse than they really are. To reduce their impact it is important to evaluate our negative thoughts and replace them with accurate onces\n\nYou can use this exercise whenever you experience negative thoughts.", "prompt_time": -1, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 15}, {"question_text": "Do you think this exercise could be useful in dealing with unpleasant thoughts?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "prompt_time": -1, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": null, "question_id": 16}, {"question_text": "Congratulations.\n\n You have finished \"Thought Shakeup\" Exercise", "prompt_time": -1, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 17}]}], "id": "THOUGHT_SHAKEUP", "end_timestamp": 1490305057551}'
1490305149631,-360,'{"status": "COMPLETED", "start_timestamp": 1490305061297, "name": "Thought Shakeup", "trigger_type": "USER", "question_answers": [{"status": "COMPLETED", "completion_time": 1490305144928, "start_time": 1490305071643, "questions": [{"question_text": "The unpleasant thoughts that cross our minds are often exaggerated or inaccurate.\n\nThe following exercise is designed to help you shakeup your thoughts. You can use it to evaluate your thoughts, examine how accurate they are, and replace them with more accurate thoughts.", "prompt_time": 1490305073585, "completion_time": 1490305072673, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 0}, {"question_text": "Think about an unpleasant thought you are currently having.\n\nPlease type that thought in the box below. You can still continue with the exercise even if you don''t type anything.", "prompt_time": 1490305074119, "completion_time": 1490305073581, "question_type": "edittext", "response": null, "question_id": 1}, {"question_text": "How true do you believe this thought is?", "prompt_time": 1490305074622, "completion_time": 1490305074096, "question_type": "seekbar", "response": ["50"], "question_id": 2}, {"question_text": "On the following screens there are some questions regarding your thought.\n\nThere are no correct or incorrect answers. Please select the response that seems most correct for you.", "prompt_time": 1490305076943, "completion_time": 1490305074590, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 3}, {"question_text": "My thought is based on a \"all-or-nothing\" or \"extreme\" view. For example, \"If I am not the absolute best, it means I''m worthless\".", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490305077830, "completion_time": 1490305076937, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Agree"], "question_id": 4}, {"question_text": "My thought is affected by my focus on the negative aspects of the situation rather than the whole picture.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490305078633, "completion_time": 1490305077816, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Neither agree or disagree"], "question_id": 5}, {"question_text": "My thought is affected by the idea that everything is related to me or caused by me. It doesn''t take into account external circumstances or other people''s responsibility.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490305079987, "completion_time": 1490305078615, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Agree"], "question_id": 6}, {"question_text": "My thought is affected by what I''ve decided others think about me, even if this is not what they really think.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490305080830, "completion_time": 1490305079981, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Agree"], "question_id": 7}, {"question_text": "My thought does not take into account my successes or good qualities.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490305081628, "completion_time": 1490305080819, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Neither agree or disagree"], "question_id": 8}, {"question_text": "My thought is influenced by the overly negative consequences I think certain events or conditions will have on my future.", "response_option": ["Strongly Agree", "Agree", "Neither agree or disagree", "Disagree", "Strongly Disagree"], "prompt_time": 1490305096402, "completion_time": 1490305081608, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Agree"], "question_id": 9}, {"question_text": "In the box below, use the provided sentence starters to come up with reasons why your thought may be correct or incorrect.\n(please click \"done\" to continue)", "prompt_time": 1490305097334, "completion_time": 1490305096396, "question_type": "edittext_special", "response": ["hhbj", "jhh", "jbj", "jhh"], "question_id": 10}, {"question_text": "Please take a moment to review your answers to the previous questions and reflect on how your thought might be phrased differently taking these answers into account.", "prompt_time": 1490305119868, "completion_time": 1490305097305, "question_type": "text_review", "response": null, "question_id": 11}, {"question_text": "Try rephrasing your thought in a way that reflects reality as accurately as possible. The new wording does not need to be more positive, just more realistic.", "prompt_time": 1490305128720, "completion_time": 1490305119842, "question_type": "edittext", "response": ["quitting smoking is just one step of getting healthy"], "question_id": 12}, {"question_text": "How correct is your new thought\n(Touch and drag)", "prompt_time": 1490305136240, "completion_time": 1490305128711, "question_type": "seekbar", "response": ["90"], "question_id": 13}, {"question_text": "Read your original thought again. How correct do you think it is?\n(Touch and drag)", "prompt_time": 1490305139839, "completion_time": 1490305136214, "question_type": "seekbar", "response": ["29"], "question_id": 14}, {"question_text": "Our negative thoughts often make things seem worse than they really are. To reduce their impact it is important to evaluate our negative thoughts and replace them with accurate onces\n\nYou can use this exercise whenever you experience negative thoughts.", "prompt_time": 1490305143514, "completion_time": 1490305139818, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 15}, {"question_text": "Do you think this exercise could be useful in dealing with unpleasant thoughts?", "response_option": ["Yes", "No"], "prompt_time": 1490305143522, "completion_time": 1490305143508, "question_type": "multiple_choice", "response": ["Yes"], "question_id": 16}, {"question_text": "Congratulations.\n\n You have finished \"Thought Shakeup\" Exercise", "prompt_time": 1490305143518, "completion_time": 0, "question_type": "text", "response": null, "question_id": 17}]}], "id": "THOUGHT_SHAKEUP", "end_timestamp": 1490305149627}'
1490922783322,-360,'{"status": "MISSED", "start_timestamp": 1490922783290, "name": "Thought Shakeup", "trigger_type": "SYSTEM", "id": "THOUGHT_SHAKEUP", "end_timestamp": 1490922783290}'
